O.k., perfect we're going to get started in a second.
I know a lot of ladies out there are wondering, "How do I get my skin clean?
How do I get rid of this makeup?"
Well, today I'm going to show you how.
My name is Sylvia Russell and today we're going to show you how to clean your face and get rid of makeup.
Now make sure that you have the proper products; cleansing gel, cleansing wash, whatever you like on your skin, make sure you have it handy.
Make sure you have water and you have a towel or some paper towels and cotton to help you clean up.
So what you're going to do is go ahead and begin to wash your face.
Now remember, cleansing the skin is something that can be very easily done at home, and it's something that you want to do on a regular basis.
Removing makeup is vital.
We don't want to sleep all night with makeup on our skin, because this can cause breakouts and acne on the skin.
So make sure to use a good cleansing product when removing makeup.
Makeup is something that all women love to use but we also need to remember to remove it properly.
Simply apply the cleanser or cream to your hands and apply it to the face and begin rubbing.
Now remember, getting rid of that makeup you might have to cleanse twice.
So don't be afraid to go back over your face again a second time.
Remember, cleansing your skin is very easy and you can do it yourself at home.
My name is Sylvia Russell and this is how you can clean your skin and get rid of makeup.